(忆往昔)
Sammy受伤了
Sammy's hurt.
他伤得很严重
He's hurt real bad.
这条祈祷面向所有能听得到的天使
This one goes out to any angel with their ears on.
我是Dean Winchester
This is Dean Winchester.
我需要帮助
And I need your help.
先告诉我你叫什么
Start with a name.
Ezekiel
Ezekiel.
我有办法治好你弟弟
There's a chance I can fix your brother.
怎么治
How will it work.
我可以在自己疗伤的同时 治愈Sam
I heal Sam while healing myself.
Sam可以随时驱逐我
Sam can eject at any time.
如果Sam驱逐了我
And if Sam does eject me.
他就会死
He will die.
那咱们就把这事儿保密
Then we keep it a secret for now.
我只希望
I just got to hope that.
你是个好人
You're one of those good guys.
我是
I am.
Zeke
Zeke.
救救她
You gonna bring her back.
就像你救活了Cass那样
Like you did with Cass.
我不能这样做
I cannot keep doing that.
为什么
Why the hell not.
每次我使用能量
Every time I use my power.
都会削弱我的力量
It weakens me.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
爸爸想让我们继续他未竟的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
帮助别人 杀魔除怪
Saving people,hunting things.
家族事业
The family business.
Becky 我写的都是真的
Becky,it's all real.
我就知道
I knew it.
那是胸吗
Nipples.
我们居然猎杀怪物
I mean,come on,we hunt monsters.
我为什么会在这儿
Why am I here.
正常人看见怪物会撒腿就跑
I mean,normal people they see a monster and they run.
但咱们不可以 不要啊
Not us...no,no,no.
咱们睁着眼睛往虎口里钻
We search out things that want to kill us.
这是真的 是真的
It's real,it's real.
你的死期到了
Now,you die.
你知道什么人才这么干吗
You know who does that.
神经病
Crazy people.
我是蝙蝠侠
I'm Batman.
我们脑子有病
We are insane.
我把鞋丢了
I lost my shoe.
太可怕了
That was scary.
比赛只剩下一分二十秒了 现在是62比54
And with a 1:20 left in the game,it's 62-54.
这一队很想获得冠军
This team wants that championship.
很厉害
It would be great.
他得分了
He's up.
太棒了 但是裁判吹哨了
It's good,but the ref's on the whistle.
他犯规了 应该是撞人了
He's calling a foul.It could be charging.
十号 他可能对此不开心
Number 10,he's not happy about that.
这家伙可能会被罚出场
This guy just about could foul out.
除了裁判没人希望他被罚出场
And nobody but the ref wants to see that happen.
Johnson教练看着时钟
Coach Johnson watching the clock.
他要求暂停
He calls time-out.
正在跟裁判说话
Talking to the ref right now.
目前这场比赛中
You know, so far in this game
(权利的游戏)
只有一名球员被裁判
There have been a number of fouls called.
罚出场 而这不是
By this particular ref,and that's not.
别大惊小怪 Colonel
Easy,Colonel.
谁在那儿
Is anyone here.
每次都能吓着我
Gets me every time.
怎么了 伙计
What's the matter,boy.
是我啊
It's me.
见鬼
What the hell.
怎么了
What.
Kevin
Kevin.
他刚给自己灌了水牛奶
Just poured some buffalo milk down his gob.
两杯
Twice.
水牛奶吗
Buffalo milk.
对的 宿醉良药
Yeah.Hangover cure-all.
里面什么都有
It's got everything in it.
就是没有水牛奶
Except buffalo milk.
他还没恢复过来吗
How's that kid still recovering from Branson.
我能说什么 那小子太新手了
What can I say,he's a amateur.
就在餐厅里喝的那两杯
The slippery nipple shot at the.
差点儿要了他的命
Dolly Parton Dixie Stampede nearly killed the guy.
好吧
All right.
我找到了点儿东西
Well,I got something that's gonna.
能让咱回归老本行
Get us back on the road.
案子吗
A case.
没错
Yeah.
你确定你准备好了吗
You sure you're ready for that.
我为什么没准备好
Why would I not be ready for that.
你不是一直精神不大好吗
Aren't you kind of running on empty.
但是在过去的3天里
Yeah,but the last three nights straight.
我每天都能睡8个小时
I had eight hours of shut-eye.
对于一个猎人来说 这简直超神了
And for a hunter,that's like 20.
相信我 Dean
And trust me,Dean.
我现在好极了
I feel good.
那真是太好了 James Brown
Well,that's great and all,James Brown.
但你还没从试炼里恢复过来
But you're still recovering from the trials.
我觉得你应该慢慢来
I think you ought to pace yourself,you know.
你恢复得越快
And the sooner you heal.
然后呢
Yeah.
我只是想让你早日恢复以前的状态
I just want you back to your old self.
我已经好了
I am.
Dean 听着
Dean,look.
Kevin现在恢复正常了
Kevin's back on the heaven stoke.
Crowley被咱们关起来了
Crowley's locked up.
咱们应该做回自己的老本行
We should be out there doing what we do best.
你到底想不想听
You want to listen at least.
好极了
Okay,great.
动物标本制作商
Taxidermist named Max Alexander.
Max Alexander 被神秘撞死
Mysteriously crashed to death.
身体几乎被完全肢解
Nearly every joint in his body dislocated.
全身骨骼破裂
Every bone broken.
完全变成了椒盐脆饼
Poor guy's a human pretzel.
来说说什么东西能做到这种程度
You tell me what's got that kind of strength.
神奇的墨西哥摔角选手
A demonic Luchador.
那家店离咱们就几小时车程
Shop's a couple hours away.
就在俄克拉荷马州的伊尼德 至少去查看一下
In Enid Oklahoma,we should at least check it out.
除非你有充分的理由证明不应该去
Unless there's some reason you think we shouldn't
(动物标本店 提供邮寄)
真精致
Subtle.
看看这个
Check that out.
真是越来越诡异了
The creep factor just skyrocketed.
你好
How're ya.
Michaels探员和Deville探员
Agent Michaels and Deville.
尸体已经被送去太平间了
Body's already been to the morgue.
刚跟Dave Stephens聊过
Just wrapping up with Dave Stephens.
是他发现了尸体
He's the one who discovered the body.
我以前和Max一起打猎呢 真遗憾
Such a shame,I used to go hunt with Max.
他人很好
He's real good egg.
节哀顺变
Sorry for your lost.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不介意带我搭档四处查看一下吧
You mind showing my partner around.
我有几个问题要问Stephens先生
I just got a couple questions for Mr.Stephens.
没问题 跟我来
Okay,come on.
你是Dave Stephens吗
Hey,Dave Stephens.
如果你可以的话
I just got a couple questions for you.
我有几个问题要问你
If that's all right.
我会把你想知道的都告诉你的
I'll tell you whatever you need to know.
Max他
Max was a.
是个非常好的家伙
A real pal.
结伴打猎吗
Hunting buddy.
我猜的
Lucky guess.
你是什么时候发现尸体的
So about what time did you discover the body.
早上9点左右
About nine a. m.
是我提货的时间
At my usual pickup time.
我每周三和周日
I come in every Wednesday and Sunday.
都回来收内脏
To collect the entrails.
收什么
The what.
动物器官
The animal organs.
Max把尸体剖开
After Max would dig'em out.
然后制作标本
And work his magic.
他
He.
他是个艺术家
He was a real artist,you know.
不过奇怪的是
Strange thing is,though.
今天早上垃圾桶是空的
Bins were empty this morning.
这怎么奇怪了
Why is that strange.
因为今天是周日
Cause it's a Sunday.
周末打猎 在这片区域来说
Weekend hunts are pretty much a.
基本上是大丰收
Given in the neck of the woods.
所以垃圾箱应该塞满内脏才对
So they're usually chock-full of guts.
有没有可能是Max自己已经清理过了呢
Any chance Max could have cleaned them out himself.
不可能
No.
那东西有的有毒
It is a biohazard.
你不能就这么轻易把它们清理干净
You can't just,you know,throw the stuffs out.
得用火烧
You got to burn it.
店里有没有其他东西报失
Is there anything else missing from the shop.
没有
No.
外来人员登记很完整 保险箱完好无损
The register was full and safe was intact.
Max所有的作品都完好的待在墙上
And all of Max's trophies were still on the walls.
除了你还有别人来过吗
Were there anybody else here when you showed up.
没有了
No one.
当然
Well,other than.
除了 Colonel
The Colonel.
失陪了
Excuse us.
那么
So.
咱们找到了个喜欢收集动物器官的贼
Okay,so we got a thief who's jonesing for animal parts.
奇怪的符号
We got a pagan symbol.
还有一块人肉卷饼
We get a human pretzel.
是啊 这事儿很像是巫师干的
Yeah,it all sounds very witchy.
但是我没找到任何巫术袋
But I wasn't able to find a hex bags.
好吧 咱们再继续查一查
All right,well,let's keep digging.
但是
But.
不在这儿
Not here.
我不喜欢它看着我的眼神
Don't like the way that one's looking at me.
好了
Okay.
那个涂鸦并不是巫术
Symbol in the graffiti,it's not wiccan.
其实是个商标
It's copywritten.
当地动物权益保护协会
Local Animal-Rights Group.
伊尼德对PETA(善待动物组织)的回应
Enid's answer to PETA.
S. N. A. R. T.
(善待所有生物)
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me.
一群动物保护主义者跟标本制作商有仇
It makes sense that an animal-rights group.
这事儿还挺容易理解的
Would have an axe to grind with a taxidermist.
为什么
Why.
那些动物本来就死了呀
The animal's already dead.
是这样没错 但是猎人们可以继续
Yeah,but hunters are what.
支持着整个行业
Keep them in business.
现在的问题是
Now the question is.
这帮动物保护主义者到底是巫师
Are those bleeding hearts actually witches.
还是一帮乱涂鸦的小混混
Or just hippies.
有什么区别吗
What's the difference
(和谐地球 素食烘烤店)
我就知道万恶之源
Always knew I'd find the source of all evil.
会潜伏在素食店里
At a vegan bakery.
什么味道
What's that smell.
广藿香
A patchouli.
混合着因为缺少肉食而产生的怨气
Mixed with depression from meat deprivation.
嘿
Hey.
知道什么人才在室内戴墨镜吗
You know who wears sunglasses inside.
盲人
Blind people.
和傻逼
And douchebags.
是Olivia
Olivia.
和Dylan Camrose吗
And Dylan Camrose.
有什么能帮助您的吗
At your service.
你们是S. N. A. R. T. 的成员吗
You two are remembers of S. N. A. R. T.
事实上 是组织者和联合主席
Founders and co-presidents actually.
有没有兴趣拿点儿资料看看
Can we interest you in some literature.
或者来一块亚麻籽司康饼
Or a flaxseed scone.
零谷物 零面粉 零糖分
It's wheat-free,gluten-free,sugar-free.
- 而且非常多汁 - 给我打住
- And suprisingly moist - Let me stop you right there.
我们是来调查
We're here to investigate.
Max Alexander的死因的
The death of Max Alexander.
当地动物标本制作商
A local taxidermist.
他死了吗
He's dead.
你认识他
You knew him.
差不多吧
Ish.
毕竟是个小镇
Small town.
他昨晚被杀了
Well,he's murdered last night.
S.N.A.R.T.的标志出现在犯罪现场
And the S.N.A.R.T. logo was found at the crime scene.
你们俩不会恰好
You two wouldn't happen to.
知道些什么内幕吧
Know anything about that,would you.
他的业务都是靠猎人搞起来的
His business is funded by hunters.
猎人都是一个德性
And you know how hunters are.
一群自负的混蛋
They're selfish dicks.
禽兽不如
Who define themselves by what they kill.
作为倡议保护动物一员
And as animal advocates.
我们无法接受他们的行为
We couldn't stand for that.
所以你们杀了他
So you killed him.
当然没有
Of course not.
S.N.A.R.T.提倡零暴力
S.N.A.R.T. doesn't tolerate violence.
零暴力就等于
This coming from a couple.
散播恐吓涂鸦吗
Who spray paints death threats.
那只是个提醒而已 我们就是想吓吓他
It was a scare tactic,we just wanted to spook him.
但结果我们自己反被吓到了
Turns out we're the ones who got spooked.
你什么意思
What does that mean.
昨天晚上
Last night.
我们俩碰头的时候
When we were tagging the joint.
我们听到了一些动静
We heard this noise.
嘶嘶的叫声
A hissing noise.
我们吓坏了 然后跑进了巷子里
It freaked us out so we ran out into the alley.
但是有人袭击了我们
But someone attacked us.
把梅斯毒气喷进了我们的眼睛里
Sprayed us in the eyes with mace.
但我俩不可能报警
And it's not like we could go to the cops.
所以现在我们看起来像两个傻逼一样
So now we will look like total douchebags.
因为我们在屋子里也戴着墨镜
Because we have to wear sunglasses inside.
坏死病吗
Necrosis.
细胞组织早亡
Premature death of tissues.
所以他们的眼睛才变成了那样
That's why their eyes were all messed up.
但并不是因为什么梅斯毒气
And it's not caused by mace.
那是什么
All right then,what cause it.
这儿写着呢
Right here.
钝物敲击 射线侵染 毒液
A blunt force,radiation,venom.
比如蛇的毒液
As in snack.
那个标本制作商被勒碎了
The taxidermist was constricted.
Olivia和Dylan听到了嘶嘶声
Olivia and Dylan heard hissing.
然后眼睛被喷洒了液体
And they were sprayed in the eyes.
毒液
By venom.
那么
Okay,so.
咱们要对付的
What are we talking here,some sort of a.
是一只奇葩蛇精
Freaky-ass snake monster.
有可能
Maybe.
但是奇怪的是
The weird thing is.
蛇要么是把猎物毒死 要么把猎物勒死
Snakes either envenomate or constrict.
这两件事不会同时发生
No snake does both.
那我更正一下
Correction.
是巨奇葩蛇精
Freaky ass mega snake monster.
可能是个Vetala干的
That could be a Vetala.
是啊 但它们可直接上嘴咬
Yeah,but they're not afraid to sink their fangs in.
标本制作商身上没有咬痕
Taxidermist was bite-free.
跟valata习性不符
Doesn't really fit the profile.
是啊
Right.
那么
So.
打给Kevin
So call Kevin.
让他查查相关资料
Have him looked some stuff up
(伊尼德动物收留中心)
你是不是来早了
Aren't you early.
老兄
Dude.
你不是香水公司的吗
You said you were from a perfume company.
不 不 不要啊
No,no,please.
有爪痕
Claw marks.
是啊 警察说所有的猫都不见了
Yeah,cops said all the cats went missing.
好吧 昨天
Right,so yesterday.
咱们对付的是个蛇精
We're dealing with some sort of a snake monster.
今天成了猫咪杀手
Today it's a killer kitty.
我不知道
I don't know.
嘿
Hey.
这个小家伙怎么这么眼熟
Why does that mutt look familiar.
它是那个标本制作商的狗
That was the taxidermist's dog.
所以 两处犯罪现场它都在
So he's been at both crime scenes.
对
Yeah.
也许它是嫌疑犯
Maybe it's a suspect.
也许
Well,may.
可能是化兽人 或许是变形怪
Could be a skinwalker,maybe a shapeshifter.
我看不像
Doesn't really look like a monster to me.
有办法试出来
One way to find out.
嗨
Hi,boy.
嘿
Hey.
乖哈 不会痛的
This isn't gonna hurt at all.
除非你被伤到
Unless it hurts.
这么说
Guess we can.
可以排除凶手了
Rule out killer.
你们还需要帮助吗
You agents need any further assistance.
警官 我们现在不需要 谢谢
Officer,I think we're okay.Thanks.
随时可以找我
Let me know.
警官 打扰一下
Officer,excuse me.
能借用你的帽子吗
Can I borrow your hat.
祝收养成功
Good luck getting adopted.
这么说
So.
Colonel不是嫌疑犯
The Colonel is not a suspect.
它是目击证人
Maybe a witness.
嘿 你懂手语吗
Hey boy,you speak sign language.
- 猴子才懂手语 - 啊
- That's monkeys - Eh.
这样吧
You know what.
说出来可能很不可思议
This is gonna sound crazy.
我读过一本书 讲一个男的
I read this book once about this guy.
在一只狗目击一场凶杀案后
Who tried to teach his dog to speak.
教狗说话
After it witnessed a murder.
成功了吗
It worked.
没有
No.
但是他还是写书了
But he wrote a book about it.
没错 他没有我们手上的资源
Yeah,he didn't have what we have.
Kevin 是我
Kevin,hey,it's me.
怎么能和狗沟通
How do we speak to a dog.
因纽特咒语
An Inuit spell.
是的
Yeah.
我们都知道 学者里面
We knew the...man of letters.
也有爱斯基摩人
Had its own Eskimo section.
这样就能跟Colonel无障碍沟通了吗
And it supposed to let us communicate with the Colonel.
是的
Yeah,well.
计划是这样的
That's the plan.
Kevin说这像是某种
Kevin said it's like a sort of a.
人与动物的思想融合
Human/animal mind meld.
- 什么意思 - 如果成功
- Meaning - If it works.
我们就能读懂Colonel的思想了
We should be able to read the Colonel's thoughts.
好吧 我来
All right,I'll do it.
- 你 - 你的麻烦已经够多了
- You - You got enough on your plate.
比如
Like what.
比如 你很疲劳
Like...you're tired.
你还在恢复当中
You're on the mend,okay.
还有
Plus,you.
你的胃比较敏感 我们现在最不需要的
You got a sensitive stomach,last thing we need.
就是你来喝这玩意儿
Is you chucking this stuff up.
看起来不算太糟
It doesn't look so bad.
我刚说错了
I was wrong.
给我
All right,come on.
咒语
Deila hér me.
Dag eru nou rar vitur orum.
好吧 那就赶快开始吧
All right,let's get this party started.
告诉我你知道的所有事
Tell me everything you know.
怎么不说话了
What's the matter?Cat got your tongue.
好吧 不好笑
Tough crowd.
给Kevin打电话
So,call Kevin.
这咒语又不好喝 还一点用都没有
Spell tasted like ass and was a buzz.
这都没影响到你的食欲 真棒
At least it didn't affect your appetite.Geez.
换台
Change the station.
快换台
什么
What.
怎么了
你 你别说话 起作用了
You...shut up!It's working.
赶紧问啊
Go.
你再说一遍
Say it again.
你管这叫经典摇滚乐吗
You call this classic rock.
他们下一首就会放Styx的歌了
Next thing you know,they'd be playing Styx.
Dennis Deyoung
And Dennis Deyoung?
只不过是朋克而已
A punk.
Dennis Deyoung不是朋克
Dennis Deyoung is not a punk.
Mr.Roboto是经典
It's Mr.Roboto,bitch.
你为什么在跟一只狗
Why are you arguing with a dog.
争论Styx乐队
About Styx.
是哦
Yeah.
嘿 亲
Hey boy.
那个牛仔帽
What were you trying to tell us.
你想告诉我们什么
About the cowboy hat.
杀我最好朋友的蠢货
The douchewheel who killed my best friend.
戴了一顶牛仔帽
Was wearing a cowboy hat.
还杀了长发嬉皮士吗
And the pothead,too.
对的
Yep.
是同一个人作案
Same guy killed both.
问问猫
Ask about the cat.
那些猫去哪儿了
What about the cats.
- 我不知道 - 我不想要这坨纸
- I don't know - I don't want this.
我没看见多少
I couldn't seen much.
我那个位置在收养所里又不是最佳观景区
I didn't exactly have the best view in the orphanage.
但是我能闻出来
But I could smell him.
那家伙身上有生肉的味道 洗洁精的味道
Guy reeked of red meat,dishwashing detegent and.
还有万金油的味道
Tiger Balm.
它说什么
So,what's he saying.
说 那个凶手
That the...guy.
有生肉的味道
He smelled like ground chuck.
肥皂水
Soap suds.
老妇霜的味道
Old lady cream.
Dean 你在干什么
Dean,what are you doing.
我不知道
I don't know.
你笑什么
What're you laughing at.
嘿
Hey.
喂喂
Hey,hey.
你
Yeah,you.
说你呢
You.
喂喂
Hey!Hey.
你别跑 就你
You!You!You.
你玩哪儿走 汪
You.
呃 Dean
Ummmm,Dean.
我觉得咒语成功了
I think the spell worked.
但是 成功得有些过了
Fact,I think it worked a little too well.
什么
What.
你觉得 你可能 变成狗了
I think you might be a dog.
- 你说什么 - 你挠你耳朵
- What - You're scratching your head.
对邮递员吼
You're...barking at the mailman.
还喜欢把扔出去的东西捡回来
You playing fetch.
我
I.
汪汪
Ruh-roh.
不是 好
No,that...Okay.
好的 谢谢
All right,thanks.
所以说 这咒语是有副作用的
So,apparently the Inuit spell has some side effects.
我喝之前怎么不说
Oh,it'd have been nice to know before I downed it.
什么副作用
What kind of side effects.
你跟动物思想融合的时候
When you mind meld with an animal,it's.
有可能会表现出 该动物的习性
Possible to start exhibiting some of its behavior.
别看我啊 Hoss
Don't look at me,Hoss.
又不是我的错
It ain't my fault.
我还有多久会想
How long am I gonna have the urge to.
闻屁屁
Sniff butts.
我才不想闻
I don't have the urge to sniff butts.
现在不想
Yet.
- 你真的想 - 没有
- Do you really have the - No.
怎么可能
Come on.
Kevin也不知道咒语会持续多久
Kevin doesn't know how long it'll last.
你也知道 这不属于科学领域
It's not like it's exact science,you know.
希望咒语失效之后
But hopefully when the spell wears off.
副作用也随之而去
So will the side effects.
我要是你 我就不吃
I wouldn't eat that if I were you.
你真打算吃巧克力整死自己吗
Chocolate?Seriously.
我们去哪儿
Where we headed.
回收留中心去
Back to the shelter.
闻线索吗
To sniff out more clues.
还是挖漏掉的信息
Maybe dig up something we missed.
你要再说犬界的双关
All right,one more doggy pun out of you.
我就把你阉了
And I'm gonna have your nuts clipped.
我不得不跟你说实话
I hate to break it to you.
我已经寂寞空虚很久了
My sack's emptier than Santa's after Christmas.
玩儿我呢吗
Oh,are you kidding me.
滚开 蠢鸽子
Hey,dick move,pigeon.
去死吧 脑残
Screw you,asshat.
- 它 - 怎么了
- Did - What.
等等 我是不是能听懂所有动物的话
Wait a minute,can I hear all animals.
对啊 动物界的有通用语言
Yup,animals have a universal language.
就像世界语
Like esperanto.
这只就碰上了
But this one actually caught on.
我才刚刚开始
And I'm just getting started,too.
我要来个大的
Brewing a real big one.
你的车过后肯定像糊了一层奶油一样白
Bet your ride's gonna look sweet in white.
- 它在说什么 - 你
- What's he saying - You.
这鸽子脑子有问题
He's being a douchebag.
你说谁脑子有问题 脑残
Who you calling douchebag,douchebag.
闭嘴 你这带翅膀的老鼠
Oh,shut it,you winged rat.
- 哥啊 - 干什么
- Dude - What.
你就 冷静一下
Just...calm down.
上车吧
Just get in the car.
哈哈 对啊
Ha,that's right,Sally.
找妈妈哭去吧
Go cry to mama.
够了 你这狗娘养的
That's it,you son of a bitch.
Dean 快进车里
Ooh!Dean!Hey!Get in the car.
我想把Colonel留在车里会比较好吧
I think it's probably best to just leave Colonel in the car.
你说什么
Excuse me.
窗户都是开着的
All the windows are open.
你觉得我们喜欢那样吗
You think we like that.
我们
We.
你觉得就因为窗户是开的
You think because the windows are open.
这就算是某种款待了是吗
That that's some sort of a treat,huh.
狗跟我们一起进去
No,the dog's coming in.
别那么冲
Respect.
长得不错
Yeah,baby.
没错
You said it.
Dean
Dean.
关于那个戴牛仔帽的男人
So,what else can you tell me.
你还知道些什么
About the man with the cowboy hat.
说实话 我看到的不多
Honestly,I couldn't see much.
可恶的白内障
Damn cataracts.
还没有人付我的手术费
And you know no one's going to pay for my surgery.
只不过又是一起伤亡而已
Just another casualty of the system I guess.
我不属于这里
I don't belong here,you know.
我是纯种的
I'm pedigreed.
我相信你很快就会出去的
Well,I'm sure you'll be out of here soon.
别逗了 我都14岁了
Please,I'm 14.
祝好运
Good luck...Ma'am.
他们每天都要清理一次
Once the day they clean these cages.
- 每天一次 - 好吧
- Once a day - Okay.
我要吃饼干
Biscuit,Just one biscuit.
我要拉寇儿薇芝的海报和摇滚乐
I need a Raquel Welch poster and a rock hammer.
我要摇坏这栅栏
I'm shaking the fence,boss.
我还在摇
Still shaking the fence.
- 我在这 - 我是被陷害的
- Over here - I was framed.
有发现吗
Any luck.
基本没有
Hardly.
没有任何线索
I'm not getting any clues.
只是一堆抱怨
Just bunch of complaints.
嘿 帅哥 过来
Hey,pretty boy.Over here.
呃 很抱歉
Yeah,ummm,sorry pal.
我今天的工作结束了
I'm done for the day.
但是我什么都看见了
But I saw everything.
我可以告诉你们 只是
And I'll tell you,but.
不是免费的
It'll cost you.
开什么玩笑
Wait,you kidding me.
我要被一只狗敲诈了
I'm being extorted by a dog.
你要什么
What do you want.
要什么 希望被带走 还是要品牌世佳的食物
What?Beggin' strips?Snausages.
那是婊子才要的好吗 如果我要告密揭发某人
Bitch please.If I'm gonna rat someone out.
就必须是让我觉得值得的事
It's got to be worth my while.
我要 挠肚子
I want...a belly rub.
好吧
You...all right.
不是你挠
Not from you,sweetie.
要那个大个子
From that big one.
那边
Over there.
牛仔帽 皮裤
A cowboy hat,leather pants.
这家伙肯定是还没出柜
Dude's a totally closet case.
除了他的衣着 还有
Okay,what else can you tell me about the guy.
其他什么吗
Other than...his outfit.
他给猫带了一个粗麻袋
He was carrying a burlap sack for the cats.
他要猫干什么的
What does he want with the cats.
真舒服 我怎么知道 但是他把猫全带走了
Atta boy.Hell if I know,but he took all of them.
有一只被他吃了
Except for the one he ate.
什么
What.
我们要找的凶手牙口不错
Apparently our guy's a sweet tooth.
小猫咪都不在话下
For kitty cats.
麻袋上面有写字
And the sack had something written on it.
上面写的什么
Okay,what did it say.
喂 我们说好的
Hey,come on,we had a deal.
你跟这大个子说说
Well,you tell that to the tall drink.
是他先停下的
He's the one who stopped rubbing.
Sam
Sam.
我手都抽筋了
Hand cramps.
它不吭声了
She's not talking.
这就对了
Atta boy.
上面写着前卫餐厅 你走运了
It said Avant-Garde Cuisine.Lucky for you.
我看得懂法语
I read French.
那是主街道上的一家餐厅
That's a cafe on Main Street.
宠物不得入内
No dogs allowed.
怪不得他身上有汉堡包味道和洗洁精的味道
No wonder he smelled like hamburgers and dish soap.
我们要进城一趟了
So,we got to go downtown.
显然我们要找的人在餐厅里工作
Apparantly our guy works at a restaurant.
嗯
Yeah.
等等等
Wait,wait,wait.
你们确定不收养我吗
Sure you don't want to adopt me.
不需要 谢谢
No thanks.We'll pass.
别走 我不会舔脚的
No,I'm not above licking feet.
嘿 大个子 回来
Hey,big'un,come back here.
好了
All right.
等等
Hey hold up.
怎么了
What's the matter.
我试过的最舒服的挠挠
Best belly rub I ever had.
自由啦
Freedom.
我给动物管理中心留了个惊喜
I left a superise in there for animal control.
我不知道你还是个傻子
I didn't peg you for a softy.
回家了回家了
Going home,I'm going home.
宝贝儿我回来了
Honey I'm coming home.
回家了
Yeah,I'm coming home.
烟肉 烟肉 烟肉
Bacon!Bacon!Bacon!Bacon.
我想问
I'm sorry.
谁家这么有钱 星期一都不营业
Who can afford to be closed on Monday these days.
- 杀人的疯子 - 对
- A homicide maniac - Yeah.
这边
Hey.
看
Check this out.
Leo警长
Chef Leo.
是他吗
Think he's our guy.
这里是乡下
It's okie town.
很多男的都戴牛仔帽
Lots of dudes were cowboy hats.
羟可酮 曲马多 美沙酮
Oh,oxycodone,tramadol,methadone.
看来他喜欢舒舒服服的麻木着
Guess he likes to cook comfortably numb.
嗯 对
Yeah,apparently.
- 救命 - 请救救我们 先生
- Help us - Please mister.
在这里
Over here.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that.
好像小孩儿的声音
Sound like little kids.
救命 如果你不救我们
Help!If you don't free us.
- 主厨会吃了我们的 - 它说的是真的
- The chef will eat us - She's not lying.
我们在笼子里
We're in the cage.
吃了你们
Eat you.
看看你身后的冰箱
Look at the refrigerator behind you.
是的 在你身后
Yeah,behind you.
在冰箱里
In the fridge.
嘿
Hey.
猫头鹰脑袋
Owl brains.
猎豹肝脏
Cheetah liver.
灰熊心脏
Grizzly heart.
咒语书
A spell book.
萨满教
Shamanism.
主厨要用巫术来干嘛
What's the chef doing dabbling with witchcraft.
这里写着 不管你吃下动物的任何器官
It says here,whatever animal organs you ingest.
正确地混合巫毒和香料
With the right mix of hoo doo and spices.
你就能暂时获得该动物的能力
You temporarily gain the power of that animal.
那么
So,okay.
如果你吃了猫头鹰大脑
If you're munching on owl brains.
你的脑袋就能转的跟驱魔人一样了
Your head spins around like The Exorcist.
差不多
Close.
可以让你的IQ激增
Bolsters your IQ,okay.
吃下猎豹肝脏就能获得速度
Eat a cheetah liver for speed.
灰熊心脏获得力量
Bear heart for strength.
如果他吃了这些东西
Okay,so if he's chowing down on this stuff.
这样就能解释
Then it'd make sense,why he.
他为什么会勒死标本制作商
Constricted the taxidermist.
还挠死了收留中心的那个家伙
And clawed the guy in the shelter.
别见怪 为什么会有人想吃你们呢
Oh,no offense,but why do we want to eat you guys.
- 呃 我们脊椎可折叠 - 是啊 相信我们
- Uh,we have collapsable spine - We do,promise.
看看这里
Look at this.
狮子肝脏加上鹰的心脏
Lion liver plus eagle heart.
响尾蛇的獠牙加上蟒蛇的膀胱
Rattlesnake fangs plus anaconda bladder.
他在混合各种器官
He's mixing ingredients.
小声点
Shoo!Quiet.
别嘘我 你安静点
Don't shush me!You be quiet.
我很安静
I am quite.Now.
你们是谁
Who the hell are you.
我们是卫生局的
We're from the health department.
过来检查卫生
Stopped by for an inspection.
我不知道我们有安排检查
I wasn't aware we had one scheduled.
是的 没有 这才是重点
Yeah,no,you wouldn't be,that's the point.
不是说你们下班了吗
Besides,I thought you're closed.
下班了呀 不过主厨在进行私人就餐
We are,Chef's having a private dinner.
事实上 他随时会过来的
In fact,he'll be here in any minute.
那好吧 既然这样
Oh,well then,in that case.
关闭厨房
Kitchen's shut down.
关闭 为什么
Shut down?Why.
因为你们都违反了刑法第八章第十四项条例
Because you're both in clear violation of penal code 8.14.
出去 快点
Out,come on,get out.
都给我出去
Both of you.
有什么事儿会通知你们的
We'll let you know.
好了 我去前门 你去后门
All right,I take the front,you take the back.
我们都不知道怎么杀死这家伙
We don't even know how to kill this guy.
朝他脑袋开一枪
Empty one of these in his head.
看看怎么样
See what that does.
变色龙 味道也不坏
Chameleons,aren't that bad.
尝起来有点像鸡肉
Kind of taste like chicken.
你是怎么做到的
How the hell did you do that.
- 做什么 - 别装了
- Do what? - Don't play coy.
我想知道你是什么
I wanna know what you are.
去他的章鱼鲨
Oh,screw the sharktopus.
你是我的主菜
You're my main course.
为什么这里有狗的味道
Why does it smell like dog in here.
味道是从你身上来的
That smell's coming from you.
所有的狗都应该被系上项圈拴起来
All dog should be leashed.
你对我弟弟做了什么
What did you do to my brother.
你弟弟吗
Your brother.
你妈妈怀你们俩的时候
What was your mom smoking.
到底磕了什么药
When she had you two.
他没事
He's fine.
只是在晚饭前小憩一下罢了
He's just taking a little cat-nap before dinner.
我从没吃过人类心脏
I've never had human heart before.
听说挺难嚼的
Heard it's a bit chewy.
幸好我不怎么挑食
Good job I'm not a fussy eater.
你绝对是有病
You're sick.
经常有人这么说
Told that once or twice.
不不 不是指你心理变态
No,no,not in the head I.
呃 你确实有点儿变态
Well,you're that,too,but.
但我说的是 像癌症那种病
I mean sick like cancer.
看来狗真的什么都闻得出来
Oh,I guess dog really can sniff it out.
癌症第四期
Stage four carcinoma.
所以你才做了这些事
So that's why you're doing this.
发生什么事了
What happened.
倒霉到家 决定放手一搏吗
Draw a short straw,decided to break bed.
当我被确诊的时候
So when I was diagnosed.
正常的治疗过程已经无法治好我了
I was way past standard treatment.
没人能救我
No one could save me.
但是有了个波尼族萨满的帮助
But then with a help of a Pawnee Shaman.
以及一张动物园年卡 我找到了疗法
And a zoo membership,I found a cure.
只是暂时性的
Would be the temporally one.
癌症总会复发
Cancer always came back.
所以你开始用各种器官做实验吗
You're starting experimenting with different organs,huh.
给自己混了一大盘子肉当解药吃是吗
Taking a single serving for a combo platter.
我还能说什么呢
What can I say.
结合各种疗法是有效的
Combination therapy works.
我变得更强壮 而且效果
I felt stronger,and the effect.
持续很长
Lasted longer.
所以你就觉得自己可以随意杀人了是吗
And if you smoke a few innocent people in the process.
哦没错 因为你自我感觉超级良好
Well hell,at least you felt better.
我没想杀人的
I didn't mean to kill anyone.
本来没想杀
At first.
但如果有人挡了我的路
But if people got in my way.
他们就变成了附带损害品
They became collateral damage.
我猜你干掉的猎食者已经够多了
Guess you've eaten enough predators.
多到自己也开始变成猎食者了
Start to become one.
人如其食 对吧
You're what you eat,right.
即使你真的通过这样的方式 获得了别人的力量
You really think the power you hold over people's lives.
也无法弥补你本身的缺陷
Can make up for what you lack in your own.
那么 狗崽子
So,dog boy.
我要吃下什么才能打倒你呢
What do I need to eat to take you down.
你不会想这么做的
You don't wanna do this.
哦 但我确实想这么做
Oh,but I do want to do this.
看 我会杀了你
See,I'm gonna kill you.
引起食欲
Work up a nice appetite.
然后 我会吃了你弟弟
And then,I'm gonna eat your brother.
虽然我不知道他到底是什么东西
I mean I don't know what the hell he is.
但是 有那么强大的治愈能力
But with healing powers like that.
谁在乎呢
Who cares.
我要他治愈的能力
He could cure me.
犬科
Dog on.
都差不多
Sort of dog.
抱歉 狼胜过狗
Sorry,wolf trumps dog.
可能吧 但不能胜过一群狗
Maybe,but not a whole pack.
嘿
Hey.
看在上帝份上
For the love of God.
Sammy
Sammy.
Zeke
Zeke.
你们俩随便谁赶紧给我醒一个
Whoever the hell you are.
嘿 快醒醒
Hey,Come on.
别逼我舔你脸
Don't make me lick your damn face.
嘿
Hey.
来吧
Come on.
你给我们打电话说领养的事的时候
When you called us about adopting.
我们不能相信
We couldn't believe it.
你真是个小甜甜
Aren't you a sweet ass.
离远点 愚蠢的人类
Back off,tofu breathe.
你一定饿坏了
You must be starving.
你很幸运 我烤了一些培根狗狗蛋糕
Lucky for you,I baked some bacon doggy cupcake.
我跟着这两个人 会拉出芽草的
I'm gonna be pooping wheatgrass with this two.
看 我知道他们是嬉皮士怪胎
Look,I know they are hippie freaks.
但他们能给你一个好家
But they are going to give you a good home.
那是你应得的
One you deserve.
是啊 是啊
Yeah,yeah.
真希望能带你上路 但是
Wish we could take you on the road with this,but.
那不是给狗的好生活
It's no life for a dog.
算了吧
Don't sweat it.
反正我晕车
I got car sick anyway.
我之前没敢告诉你
I was afraid to tell you earlier.
我吐你车后座上了
But I barfed in your back seat.
你
You.
怎么了
What.
我会想你的 伙计
I'm gonna miss you,buddy.
我也会想你的
I'll miss you,too.
顺便说一下
And by the way.
作为一个具有狗的荣誉称号的人 你应该知道
As an honorary dog,there is something you should know.
狗其实不是人类最好的朋友
Dogs aren't really man's best friend.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about.
我知道这听起来像是阴谋论者的论调
I know it sounds like a conspiracy theory.
但是我们在这里的真正原因是
But the real reason we were put here was to.
是什么
Put here to do what.
开什么玩笑
Oh,you got to be kidding me.
咒语现在失效了
Now the spell wears off.
好吧
Okay.
怎么样
How did it go.
坏消息是 我会想那个家伙的
Well,bad news is I'm gonna miss the flea bag.
好消息是 咒语终于失效了
Good news is it looks like the spell finally wears off.
你还好吧
You okay.
那凶手把你揍得挺惨
The Stetson man got you pretty good.
是啊 我很好
Yeah,I'm fine.
我就是
I just.
我在想他说的话 没法停下
I can't stop thinking what he said.
算了吧 Sammy
Come on,Sammy.
那货脑子有泡
The guy was out of his freaking gourd.
是 但是 我是说 为什么
Yeah,but,I mean why.
他为什么会那么问
Why would he asked that.
为什么想知道我是什么
Why did he wanna know what I was.
谁知道呢
Who the hell knows.
他整个人都不正常
He's all jacked up on juice you know.
他被他不能控制的东西附身了
He was possessed by something he couldn't control.
那是
It was.
失控只是时间问题
It's a matter of time before it completely took over.
你不能跟疯子讲道理 是吧
You can't reason with crazy,right.
我不知道
I don't know.
我知道
Well,I do.
相信我 Sammy 你没什么可担心的
Trust me, Sammy, you got nothing to worry about